foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
all right what
[Music]
hang on what's
what's going on I I can't I can't get in
what's
the problem with the door no I can see
that what's the what's the problem
no but why why is why is the door locked
issue with the passcode
well I can do it what's just tell me
what's the passcode
four five six five
no it's not
five four five six six
no it's not that that's not it try four
five six seven are you are you just
making up numbers
yeah oh my God James would have to start
the show what we have to start the show
no I'm not I'm not no I'm not I'm
starting my final show in a in a
stairwell
I don't care you have to start no I'm
not gonna I can't it's show how to start
oh my God I can't believe this well okay
welcome everybody to The Late Late Show
[Applause]
oh Crown wow thanks everybody for
coming out tonight my muse and my mum
and dad are here my sisters hey I'm not
doing this it's ridiculous there's no
point doing any of that so we'll just
get to get to the guesses but let's take
a look and see what
let's take another to see what I guess
so on the show tonight here's the star
of Elf Step Brothers and the brand new
Barbie movie which is out this summer
please welcome Mr Will Ferrell to the
show hey Will how you doing
remember I can't see him come on because
I don't have a I haven't got a screen so
I can't see the dressing room checking
oh it's at the window what will is at
the window
James up here James
James well hey hey I can't hear you
listening
door open from that side can you open
the door from there hey it won't badge
it's a well-built door uh
have you tried four five six eight what
four five six eight four five six eight
yeah okay give me a minute
no no
that doesn't work well didn't work no oh
man you try four five six nine oh so
you've only done that time for this week
we're in the tube well everybody he's
here tonight and
joining us also here is one of the
biggest superstars in the world is a
three-time Grammy award winner he's my
friend he's your friend Harry Styles is
here tonight he's hi everybody hi mate
hey and terrible timing with this door
thing huh yeah because it's your last
show no yeah I know I know it's it's a
nightmare I mean what are the chances
you know absolute disaster yeah no I
know is this your last show I'm well and
where is my last show Harry thank you
very much I don't need anybody to tell
me that no one's more aware of that than
me this is a disaster James James hi
it's Will Ferrell yeah I'm gonna bash
the door down with this fire exchange
okay I'm not sure that's a great idea
just just wait wait shoot has been
resolved sorry what door
[Music]
one one
how we have done eight years here is an
absolute miracle
[Applause]
games
ladies and gentlemen all the way from
exactly where Humanity exists as a
non-divided species give it up for your
host the one the only for the last time
James
[Applause]
thank you so much
thank you
very much please have a seat please have
a seat
you are very you're very very sweet by
going to we've only got the studio for
one more hour
thank you for tuning in thank you for
being here
thank you for coming out we have a fun
show are you ready yeah you think you're
ready I'm not sure I am I'm James Gordon
for the last time this this is The Late
Late Show
[Applause]
[Music]
and certainly is thank you for tuning in
this is it Gang This is it is the final
Late Late Show in their history of CBS
and I'm telling you tonight finally we
we aren't determined to get it right
this time we are
it's unlikely
we are so happy that you're here
um my entire family is here tonight my
mum and dad are here
are you okay Mom and Dad you're holding
it together till you asked me to give
you a kiss before we came on and then I
was gone
I didn't even know you could move your
face that much since all your Botox
I didn't know that's the most in all the
photons
said to me last night and she said we'd
still be able to come out here though
won't we and I said why she said because
there's a certain collagen for my life
that I can't get at home but look even
though we have a patched show tonight
and we do we are not going to ignore
what is our sacred duty to give you the
American people the biggest most
important news stories of the day for
the final time it's the news
[Music]
of course there is only one story only
one story that the world is talking
about today and they've been talking
about it all week really
a bunch of glue a spilled on a Michigan
Highway okay you know like this story a
truck overturned don't worry no injuries
were reported but the road was unusable
for almost 24 hours look at that
I mean talk about being stuck in traffic
oh come on
[Applause]
retiring at the height of his powers you
know what I mean yeah
yeah now jokes like that and it's like
peace out
baseball yeah
here's a new story we saw researchers
have taught Birds how to make this is
true video calls right which allows them
to develop I promise you long distance
relationships chatting with another bird
that story again pet birds are better
with technology than your mum and dad
it's impressive some of the birds have
gone so good at filming themselves
they've even started and only feathers
I want to say this I truly we have a
great show for you this evening we
really really do we have we have given
it everything and I'm so thankful truly
to each and every one of you who has
watched our show night after night here
on CBS Dan Stephanie William
that's it really it's just Ian are you
ready you ready for one last ride I I I
am I am ready for one last ride but
before we I think before we wrap this up
uh there was somebody who wanted to um
there's somebody who has relied on our
show for the news I mean for for
certainly the last three four years but
I think for a long time he he just
wanted to you know send you a quick
message so
[Music]
1200 shows in eight years but after Dave
spent working for me at the White House
this is both a snack
and a gift I'm surprised it lasted eight
years in any show
who is that guy
to you Reggie and the entire team thank
you for all the joy you brought to homes
across America
[Music]
and a special thanks for never asking me
to sing in the car
can't stay worth
am we'll miss you pal
I can't wait to see what you do next
and that is amazing
that was amazing although there was a
minute in the middle when I was watching
that where I opened those photos are
going I was like wait have I died
don't do this oh no I can't what we also
have one from Trump go ahead and roll up
listen
after the break we've got a big surprise
for you don't go anywhere this is the
last time
[Applause]
[Music]
welcome back now
it's been such an emotional time an
emotional emotional time having this
show come to an end but one positive is
I may finally get a good night's sleep
oh my God
hello James
I'm watching you sleep it's three
o'clock in the morning yeah but I need
to talk to you about what well about you
leaving we're here to tell you you can't
just leave a talk show we James hosting
the network late night talk show makes
you part of a very exclusive club and if
we're gonna let you leave we need to
know you'll keep our sacred Secrets also
I hope you don't mind I barred your
mouth guard
what are you talking about what secrets
you know how we don't watch every
episode of TV or movie that our guests
around to promote you're telling me I
didn't need to watch all four seasons of
Mozart in the jungle of course we didn't
have to watch that Mozart was never even
in the jungle damn it I miss my sister's
wedding for that
fake laugh we all have for when a guest
tells a story that isn't funny
you're not going anywhere are you no of
course not I live here will you stick
around we'll be right back more James
Harden everybody
look guys I appreciate you all feeling
passionate enough to break into my home
but I promise not to reveal any of our
secrets and look now can you please
leave James have you thought this
through well what other job will allow
you to break into song and dance every
single night I don't sing and dance
every night you do it's been a lot like
a lot that's no I did nearly two years
without singing and dancing once yeah
but that was during Colvin and then as
soon as Corbett was over you did a huge
musical number with Ariana Grande about
how covet was over for more on this it's
time for a closer look
[Music]
and after that there was immediately
another lockdown okay fine
[Applause]
this may be the hardest decision in my
life but
I am leaving
in that case we're gonna have to lay out
the terms of the official exit
foreign
can't look like you're enjoying
retirement too much you're gonna grow a
beard a huge one one that says God spoke
to me from a bush
uh you know God did speak to me and he
told me I don't need to be in this bid
and don't get any big Ideas stick to
corporate gigs podcasts maybe The Masked
Singer come on this doesn't feel fat you
know when I first moved here to America
to take over this show all I would hear
was talk of the late night Wars
then I came to realize we're not at War
we're a family we've been through so
much together
when you think about it
we're just some funny boys who like to
spread some Joy
just talk about this you're embarrassing
your country okay
splitting up your ideas splitting up my
ideas yes you're leaving your show we
figure out who gets what okay what does
everybody want
I don't know
carpool karaoke
well that's it nothing I do have to have
other bits
do you think yes yes really
what about Emoji news what's that you
know we take a news headline we turn
that headline into emojis the audience
has to guess
what I mean now I'm saying it out loud
it doesn't sound like the best idea but
look I'm sorry you can't have any of my
ideas I'm not growing a beard I'm not
doing any of this well all right well in
that case you leave us no choice we
don't want to do this but we're gonna
have to revoke your invitation to the
Met Gala what
this thing is nice please
[Laughter]
[Applause]
the sheer decadence of it all no
oh thank God
it was just a dream
it's a dream
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my God
we'll be right back with Will foul and
Harry Styles everybody come on
[Applause]
[Music]
welcome back let's meet our guests
tonight please welcome to the show Mr
Harry Styles
[Applause]
styles
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
still got the show to oh
all right yeah yeah no I didn't I didn't
put that together that you want to still
use the desk
we can get by without it we can figure
it out hang on let's go to I gotta find
the question
yeah that's yeah that's it that's got it
thanks Harry don't get splinters don't
get splinters there we go perfect
absolutely we've absolutely crushed it
thank you
yeah I just I just wrongly assume
closer to me come closer to me bless you
both I am so grateful for not that well
that might be that might be a little
that might be okay no sure
I want to say uh bless you both for
being here for finding the time to uh to
come and be here on our very last Late
Late Show image the world to me that you
are both here two people I love and
adore so much
um Harry you've done so many great bits
on our show uh over the years you even
have the words late late tattooed no
thank you
and you've hosted the show twice
you played you played spill your guts
with Kendall Jenner yeah and will we
played it's actually a photo out in the
hallway there you and I played I've got
to say nobody in the history of this
show has enjoyed playing spill your guts
more than you have it was amazing you
were just eating everything like it was
a burger and fries and this is how much
will loved playing spilling us you
actually asked if we could play it one
last time
[Applause]
we have time
great thank you thank you Ian thank you
okay right so how does this work will
how does this work we've got this is so
this is why I got uh I've got bug trifle
uh Harry salmon clam juice and wasabi
smoothie
uh and of course you have bull penis
I believe is in season
each of us has a dish yes and a question
yes uh that we've never seen before
oh wow we'll decide do you want me to
start yeah you can start welcome what's
your question now that the Late Late
Show is over who is your favorite late
night host
Crow bear Seth Meyer Jimmy Fallon or
Jimmy Kimmel
who is your favorite out of all of those
I'm gonna say uh I'm going to say Seth
Meyers
[Applause]
I have to eat no but I'm gonna eat
anyway
[Applause]
bro don't eat too much
he absolutely loves this game he sees it
he actually sees it as a free dinner
that's the truth it's like Thanksgiving
yeah
right okay hurry your Harry what's your
question for yourself mine is
foreign
yes or no will there be a One Direction
reunion
[Applause]
sorry
interesting I think if uh I would never
say never to that I think uh if those
if uh I think if there was a time when
we all felt like that
what we wanted to do then then I I don't
see why we wouldn't happen
[Applause]
okay
I'm not gonna eat the thing anywhere by
the way I would not that one is that
one's rough okay here's my question
James
who is more talented
Harry Styles or
well
[Applause]
you've gotta I mean look come on
in a pinch
you know like I love I love you like
like a brother and I love Harry's house
I love sign of the times
fine line it's amazing but I I watch Elf
every Christmas
[Applause]
in this world
it's just us
can't argue with that yeah let's see
your Will Ferrell impression
[Music]
it's very good
it's very good that's how how could I
ever choose and how can I resist one
more bit of Bull's penis in my mouth
all right we'll be right back
[Music]
welcome back Harry Styles and Will
Ferrell are here now
guys are we to know uh you have both
been you have both been so incredibly
generous to our show over the years uh
will we have had some wonderful times I
remember when you came as Ron Burgundy
and I just our entire I've never seen
this is the only day I've seen as many
people in the studio as when Ron
Burgundy did stand up Harry you have
always been here stepping in to host the
show when we did the the week to launch
your show it's been amazing and uh
for me here personally there are there
are no two people I would rather be
sitting here on the last time I ever do
this than both of you and I want to
thank you very much
for being here truly I love you I love
you very very much I do I do can I just
say that
um
as a friend I'm so incredibly proud of
you for everything you've done I know I
remember when you decided to take doing
the show and watching you do it has been
incredibly inspiring to me
on a personal note you've been
a safe space for me always as a friend
and
I'm selfishly very excited that you're
coming home but
and but
um I'm so happy for you and I'm really
really proud of you and I love you
thank you
but James Court I mean you've done such
an amazing job coming into the late
night space which is incredibly crowded
incredibly competitive
such original comedy you know and
establish your place you know in America
coming from let's face a whole country
like angle
um here
and hold your own
Trump said it not me
[Applause]
no but
Bravo thank you great job
[Applause]
do you have a question for our guests
for the final times you have a question
for our guest this evening yes
thank you tonight's question goes to
uh let's make it for all of our guests
this evening
uh do you enjoy model railroading
I can't say I've ever tried it
uh it depends on what scale H O H O
scale h o not n not n yeah I I love HO
scale model railroad and find it I find
it extremely relaxing
uh those are the correct answers yes
[Applause]
welcome back now
I've been I've been thinking for a while
the last few weeks about what
I was going to say as we come to the end
of the show after this
this wonderful adventure and and I have
uh if I wanted to I've I've struggled at
times I've I've struggled to
find the words to sum up what this past
eight years has meant to me it is almost
impossible I I frankly I don't know
where to start
but I sit here now today with nothing
but love
gratitude and pride this show is
everything it is everything I ever
wanted it to be and uh I've got to tell
you if you if you like this show and
you're tuned in here in the in the
middle of the night or online I cannot
stress enough that I am I am just one
part of a big team who make this show
this incredible family here
who have made The Late Late Show and so
many of our team
here they started this show on day one
and here we are 1200 shows later and I
would like to take this moment to thank
each and every one of you who works on
this show from the bottom of my heart
for the love and the dedication that you
have given
to making this show what it is today I
love every single one of you I will
forever be in your corner always always
always I told you last night
this was never my show
this was never my show it was ours and
I'm gonna miss every single don't this
time
I'm gonna miss every single one of you
so much I wanna I wanna if you let me I
want to say uh
a huge thank you to Reggie in the band
um
when um
when Reggie said that he'd that he'd
come and he'd join the show it changed
everything for me it really really did
it changed it was the first time that I
thought we might actually be able to do
something new and fresh and I love you
so much man I love you I thank you for
taking a leap with me on this
and for putting together this
unbelievable band to Hagar Guillermo Tim
and Steve I could never have imagined it
would have been this great
and over the past few years Ian you were
you were I can't look at you while I say
this if that's all right you Ian you
were the second writer that we hired on
this show
and from the minute we met I was like I
think I've just met the funniest person
I will ever meet in my life and you have
never ever let me down and I'm so lucky
that you and Lauren are the head writers
here because
both of you your work your dedication
your your precision and your skill has
been incredible and I can't thank you
both enough
um we are very very lucky to be on a
network like CBS I cannot express how
fantastic they have been with me from
day one
it's unfathomable why they took a chance
on me to do this job I will never
understand it but they have supported
and they have loved this show and
I will be forever grateful for what
they've done for me and my
family it's been uh
it's been life-changing
it really has because
moving here to America
moving here to America eight years ago
it was a huge leap for me my family
my son was three her daughter was 12
weeks old and we now have another small
person and she's American yeah
we uh
you know we started this show we started
with Obama
then Trump
then a global pandemic and and I've
watched I've watched America change a
lot over these past few years I've
watched I've watched divisions grow and
and I've seen and I've felt a sense of
negativity bubble and it points boil
over
and I guess all I really want to say
tonight is I implore you to remember
what America
signifies to the rest of the world my
entire life it has always been a place
of optimism and joy and yes it has flaws
so many but show me a country that
doesn't show me a person that doesn't me
you all of us we are all trying to
figure this out we are every single one
of us a work in progress and just
because somebody disagrees with you it
doesn't make them bad or evil we are all
more the same than we are
different and there are so many people
there are so many people who are
who are trying to stoke those
differences and we have to try as best
we can to look for the light look for
the joy because if you do it's out there
and that's all this show
has ever been about all we've ever
wanted is just be a little a little bit
of light and levity at the end of your
day thank you for letting me do this
thank you for letting me into your home
every night
I've never taken for granted what an
absolute privilege this has been now
look when we come back
when we come back
you are gonna be absolutely shocked at
how we are going to end this show guess
what
we're going to end with a song I know
what are the chances come on back
everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
now the last guest has gone from the
Green Room and our last conversation is
done
the final rehearsal is over
and the final commercial has run no more
late late Tinder for swiping no more
torturous games for a laugh
no more risking my life on a fighter jet
or learning too much about our staff
squeezing myself into Spanx every night
for 1200 times in a row
so good night
thanks for watching
that's our show
[Music]
[Applause]
lost karaoke's been coupled and we all
came along for the right
the Lost spill your Cuts has been
swallowed and I'm still feeling nauseous
inside
and soon I will head home to London but
I'll sure miss it here in L.A
the weather my friends and those micro
green salads I claim that I eat every
day
and Reggie will no longer ask people
questions that aren't the least bit
apropos
what is the nature of time
as always
night
thanks for watching
it's our show
that's our show that producers directors
designers the ones who set the lights
and answer phones and do the edit
writing sketches working cameras
building Graphics making costumes
booking Talent mixing sound and never
getting any credit our show was a
creation of the love and dedication
shared by everyone here in the crew
I'm grateful for the eight years I spent
with them
and the eight years I spent here with
you
as the end of the show Fast approaches
gaze at the studio floor
we filled it with thousands of moments
of joy and now there won't be any more
yet I know as I look in the camera
for the very last time as your host
that each of those thousands of moments
of Joy it's the one I'll remember the
most
and part of me thinks why not stay here
forever but deep in my heart I just know
almost shows to be showing
time I was going
it's time
[Music]
thanks for watching
that's our show
thank you so much for your time
everybody I will miss you good night
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]